{
  "1" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {6} {8} + \\frac {2} {6}\\).",
    "answer" : "26/24",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {6} {8} + \\frac {2} {6} = \\frac {36} {48} + \\frac {16} {48} = \\frac {26} {24}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "2" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {7} {8} + \\frac {6} {10}\\).",
    "answer" : "59/40",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {7} {8} + \\frac {6} {10} = \\frac {70} {80} + \\frac {48} {80} = \\frac {59} {40}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "3" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {2} {10} + \\frac {4} {12}\\).",
    "answer" : "32/60",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {2} {10} + \\frac {4} {12} = \\frac {24} {120} + \\frac {40} {120} = \\frac {32} {60}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "4" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {10} {12} + \\frac {4} {9}\\).",
    "answer" : "46/36",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {10} {12} + \\frac {4} {9} = \\frac {90} {108} + \\frac {48} {108} = \\frac {46} {36}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "5" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {3} {6} + \\frac {4} {9}\\).",
    "answer" : "17/18",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {3} {6} + \\frac {4} {9} = \\frac {27} {54} + \\frac {24} {54} = \\frac {17} {18}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "6" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {4} + \\frac {2} {6}\\).",
    "answer" : "7/12",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {4} + \\frac {2} {6} = \\frac {6} {24} + \\frac {8} {24} = \\frac {7} {12}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "7" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {1} {6} + \\frac {7} {8}\\).",
    "answer" : "25/24",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {1} {6} + \\frac {7} {8} = \\frac {8} {48} + \\frac {42} {48} = \\frac {25} {24}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "8" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {5} {12} + \\frac {6} {10}\\).",
    "answer" : "61/60",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {5} {12} + \\frac {6} {10} = \\frac {50} {120} + \\frac {72} {120} = \\frac {61} {60}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "9" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {3} {6} + \\frac {3} {4}\\).",
    "answer" : "15/12",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {3} {6} + \\frac {3} {4} = \\frac {12} {24} + \\frac {18} {24} = \\frac {15} {12}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  },
  "10" : {
    "question" : "Add \\(\\frac {7} {12} + \\frac {1} {9}\\).",
    "answer" : "25/36",
    "solution" : "\\(\\frac {7} {12} + \\frac {1} {9} = \\frac {63} {108} + \\frac {12} {108} = \\frac {25} {36}\\).",
    "explanation" : ""
  }
}

